# **SANAZ ZERAATI**

Front-End Developer(React JS)

# **ABOUT ME**

A self-taught front-end developer for a year and a mature person with more than 5 years of experience with an engineering background as a GIS technician and control project manager. During this time, I realized my interest in web development and decided to enter the profession resolutely as a front-end developer with a HackYourFuture course and other educational resources.

I am a highly enthused, responsible, motivated, hardworking, and reliable person. I have experience working as part of a team and individually and extremely driven, with a clear goal to succeed. Hence, I am keen and very willing to learn and develop new skills as a Front-End Developer in your company.

### **CONTACT**

- szeraati69@gmail.com
- sanaz-zeraati.ir
- linkedin.com/in/sanaz-zeraati
- github.com/sanaz-git
- +98 914 056 7100

#### **LANGUAGE**

English (Advance) German (Basic) Persian (Native)

# **ACTIVITIES AND INTERESTS**

Hiking, Climbing, Traveling, Music

### **SKILS**

- HTML&CSS
- MaterialUI
- Javascript
- SASS
- React.js (hooks)
- Git
- REST api
- BootStrap

## **PROJECTS**

• Food App - Link

React | Context | useReducer | useParams | Rout

Shopping Cart -Link

React|Context|useReducer|useParams|Rout

Login form - Link

React | Context | Rout

• Crypto - Link

React | Context | useState

Credit Card Validator - Link

React|useState

Weather App - Link

React | useState | useParams | Charts | Rout

responsive-website - <u>Link</u>

Vanila JavaScrips

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

**Hamyar System Company** 

June 2022 - September 2022 - Kerman

React | Material-UI | Sass | AG GRID

#### **HACKYOURFUTURE CURRICULUM - Link**

June 2021 - June 2022 - SelfStudy Web Development Program

## PROJECT CONTROL MANAGER

Water & Waste Water Company September 2019 - Present

GIS SPECIALIST

Water & Waste Water Company

January 2017 - September 2019

## **EDUCATION**

#### MASTER OF SCIENCE WATER RESOURCE ENGINEERING

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2013 - September 2016

Operation Evaluation of Copula Function in Flood Frequency Analysis

### **BACHELOR OF WATER ENGINEERING**

Shahid Bahonar University of Kerman, Iran

September 2009- September 2013

Mapping underground Dam in Arid and Semi-Arid Area





